Finding Aid for the Edwin Bower Hesser Papers LSC.1071
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Negatives, ca. 1920-1946; 13.5 boxes, 0.5 oversize box
  - A. Named subjects, ca. 1942-1946
    - Jarvis, Mr., 1944 April 13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Jewel (Sister), 1946 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young woman in sweater. Includes test prints.
    - Johns, Diane, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling low-cut, strapless dress.
    - Johnson, Jackie, 1944 July 25 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young woman modeling semi-nude while covered by a large hat. Also includes shots in bathing suit and casual attire.
    - Johnston, Miss, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait or head shot of young woman in casual attire looking over bare shoulder.
    - Kauch, Leslie, 1944 March 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling semi-nude on couch, with hat, and in business attire.
    - Kirkpatrick, Sergeant and wife, 1945 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of couple. Man is dressed in military uniform.
    - Kirky, Miss, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait or head shot of woman in strapless ruffled dress and semi-formal attire.
    - Knight, Karen, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shot of woman modeling bathing suit indoors with high heels.
    - Kramer, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Kurpra, Karen, July 14 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shot of woman modeling strapless bathing suit while lying on couch.
    - La Taur, Donna, 1945 February (Box 4, Folder 13)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling bare midriff and strapless top. Includes test prints.
    - Larrabee, William and Mr. Smith, 1945 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of two different men dressed in suits. Includes test prints.
    - Lawrence, Barbara, 1945 July (Box 4, Folder 15)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and action shots of women in western wear riding a bucking horse and posing. Includes test prints.
    - Levayan, Bolivia, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man dressed in suit and casual attire.
    - Lewis, Lillian, 1945 February 2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling formal attire. Includes test prints.
    - Lincoln, Wyn, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in ruffled dress.
    - Lindley, Virgina, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling bathing suit, casual attire, and semi-nude in sheet.
    - Little, Miss, 1945 February (Box 4, Folder 20)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young woman modeling casual attire, and semi-nude in low cut dress and sheet. Includes test prints.
    - Loretta, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling ruffled dress. Includes test prints.
    - Louise, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shot of woman modeling nude outdoors at a riverbank. Includes test print.
    - LuRay, Paul-Rita, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older man in a suit.
    - Lynne, Juli, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling in short robe and high heels, sitting on stool.
    - Lyons, Maureen, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling casual blouse and attire.
    - MacDougle Children in Big Bear, CA., ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl on swing with doll, with a goat, and with a young boy. Includes test print.
    - MacNeil, Baley, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl with kitten.
    - Martin, Emily, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling semi-nude in a sheet and low cut dress.
    - Martinson, Carol, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in sweater, scarf, and stocking cap. Also include shots of woman in semi-formal attire.
    - Maymand, Mr., ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Maymord (Daughter), 1946 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl in plaid, ruffled dress. Includes test prints.
    - McCalee, Billie, 1945 June 18 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling winter wear with skis and bathing suit. Includes shots of woman outdoors trimming a tree in Asian-inspired attire..
    - McClean, Peggy and Jack, 1945 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of couple. Man is wearing navy or sailor outfit and woman is wearing flower print dress. Also includes shots of woman posing in various bathing suits.
    - McCullen, Jane, 1945 January 5 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling formal attire.
    - McNeil, Beverly, 1946 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl posing and dancing in ballerina outfit.
    - Meyer, Bob, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man working on illustrations or paintings.
    - Milady Magazine models, 1945 January, August (Box 5, Folder 1)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shots of various women modeling for a fashion magazine. Includes exterior and interior shots, mostly framed in long shot. Includes test prints.
    - Miller, Drew, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young man in suit.
    - Miller, Luther, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man with moustache in military uniform.
    - Milton, Scott, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man modeling suit, casual attire, and flexing while shirt less.
    - Moore, Cleo, 1944 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shots of woman modeling nude, bathing suit, and casual dress outdoors. Includes shots of man in loin cloth flexing and posing with woman.
    - Morris, Lieutenant, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Mountain Trip, ca. 1943-1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of mountain landscape, animals, etc. Includes prints.
    - Muller, Richard, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of infant lying on bed.
    - Murray, Dorothy in Reseda, CA, 1946 January (Box 5, Folder 9)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling casual attire and Latin-ruffled dress.
    - Murray, Rosanna, 1945 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling business attire, casual attire, and Latin-ruffled dress with sombrero.
    - Neilson, Carol, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in casual attire and formal strapless dress. Includes test prints.
    - Nelson, Peggy, 1948 February 9 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Nichols, General and wife, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older couple. Man is wearing military uniform.
    - Nierney, Roger, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man in suit smoking cigarette. Includes test prints.
    - Oland, Antonia, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in business attire.
    - Oldfile, Vicki, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling festive and international outfits.
    - O'Neil, Sharon, 1944 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling strapless ruffled dress.
    - Pauelencip, Miss., 1946 January (Box 5, Folder 18)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in sweater posing behind a fake fence.
    - Palack, Susan, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in business and formal attire.
    - Payne, Helen, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling formal attire, Latin ruffled dress, and fish net top.
    - Pedlow family, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man in suit and little girl with doll. Includes test prints.
    - Pernetti, Patty, 1944 October 26 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling semi-nude in fur coat, formal attire, Latin ruffled dress, and casual attire.
    - Phillips, 1946 July (Box 5, Folder 23)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling various low cut tops and dresses.
    - Praskoff, Lieutenant, 1944 September 27 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Preble Models tests (Joan Martin, Patti, Marilyn, and Betty), 1945 May 3 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of various women modeling bathing suits, formal attire, festive hats, and casual attire. Includes test prints.
    - Preble's Son, 1945 July 22 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young man in military uniform.
    - Prequit, Bonnie in Hastings, Long Beach, CA, 1949 July (Box 5, Folder 27)
      2.5 x 2.5" and 4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in Latin ruffled dress.
    - Redondo, Frazee, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling strapless bathing suit top.
    - Retouching tests, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling formal, sequenced dress. Includes test prints which have pencil markings indicating areas needing retouching.
    - Richardson, Jackie, 1945 December (Box 6, Folder 1)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling plaid top and short, exotic dress on couch. Includes test prints.
    - Robertson, Captain, 1944 September 27 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older man in military uniform.
    - Rodelle, Angel, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling casual attire, low cut dresses, formal attire, and veil. Includes test prints.
    - Roelaire, Milly, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in formal attire. Includes test prints.
    - Rogers, Mickey and friend, 1944 September (Box 6, Folder 5)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of two women modeling semi nude on couch and sheet, in plaid top, low cut dress, sweater, casual attire, and ruffled dress. Includes test prints.
    - Roth, Elliot, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      8 x 10" black and white negative portrait of man in plaid shirt and jeans.
    - Rowe, Peggy, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling winter wear with skis, Latin ruffled dress, and outdoors holding dog.
    - Rurick (daughter of), ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young woman in striped casual dress.
    - Ryan, Sister Dorothy, 1944 October 12 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of nun in traditional attire.
    - Salilm, Elaine, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling semi-nude in a costume with a plaid shirt. Other shots include woman in casual attire, formal attire, and posing with props. Includes test prints.
    - Sharpe, Allen, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man with moustache in suit.
    - Shaw, Mrs., 1945 January 9 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older woman in business attire. Includes test prints.
    - Shenk Document - Ideal Chemical Products, Inc., ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      4 x 5" black and white shot of a document written by A. M. Shenk regarding Ronald A. McBride's involvement as a chemist in the company mentioned
    - Sherwood, Mr., ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Silk, Miss, 1944 April (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Skelly, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man in striped sweater and suit.
    - Smith, Claudia, 1946 January (Box 6, Folder 17)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling fur hat, low cut ruffled dress, casual attire, and head scarf.
    - Smith, Jo-Anne, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young woman in casual dress.
    - Spaeth, Betty Lee, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in sweater.
    - Spurlock, Barbara, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling strapless top and skirt, semi nude on couch, and sweater.
    - Spurlock, Mr. and Mrs. with Hazel Conley, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling various low cut tops and short dresses. Also includes solo shots of man in suit and with woman.
    - Stacey, Elaine, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of photographic prints of woman modeling formal attire, Latin ruffled dress, veil, and casual attire.
    - Starke, Pauline, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older woman in formal and business attire. Includes test prints.
    - Starres, Merideth, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      6.75 x 4.75" black and white portrait shot of woman wrapped in sheet. Includes test print. Print includes re- touching directions.
    - Stevens, Richard, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man in suit. Also includes shot of dog.
    - Sunderland, Delilah, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait or head shot of woman modeling bathing suit top.
    - Swisher, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl in bonnet and formal attire. Includes test prints.
    - Terri, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman in casual dress.
    - Toler, Mr. and Mrs. Sydney, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Townzell, Lieutenant, 1945 March (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Treul, Bob, 1944 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young man in suit, sweater, and dress shirt. Includes test prints.
    - Tripp, 1946 June (Box 6, Folder 32)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl in dress with flowers in hair.
    - Udell, Mr., 1944 September 22 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man in suit, dress shirt, and military uniform. Also includes shots of man dressed up as a circus clown referencing pictures of man in military uniform. Includes test prints.
    - Van Bryne, 1944 December 8 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of man in western wear and suit. Includes test prints.
    - Vaughn, Kerrie, 1944 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shots of woman modeling short skirt, ruffled dress, business attire, and bathing suit.
    - Vogel, John, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older man in formal suit. Includes shots of man smoking cigarette.
    - Walters, Selene, 1945 September (Box 7, Folder 4)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman modeling low cut top, strapless ruffled dress, and large sun hat. Includes test prints.
    - Wayne, Jane, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young woman in sweater.
    - Weleer, Bob, 1944 April 17 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of boy in Boy Scouts uniform. Includes test prints.
    - White, Baby, 1944 July 23 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of young girl in formal dress. Includes test prints.
    - White, Mrs. and Janet, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of woman holding young girl in formal dress and shots of unidentified woman in formal hat. Includes test prints.
    - Yoden, Ann (Eve), 1945 April 20 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shots of woman modeling bathing suit in front of columns and while sitting on stool.
    - Yoho, Virginia, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      4 x 5" black and white portrait shots of woman modeling semi-nude in transparent sheet, and in lingerie.
    - Zahn, Mr. and Mrs., ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of older smiling couple dressed in formal attire. Man is bald with thin moustache. Includes test prints.
    - Terry, Alice, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Brew, Jane (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Grey, Yvonne (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Winsor, Claire (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Hall, Lilian (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Terry Alice, Jane Brew, and Dora B., 1925 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Mary Brian, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Gwen Ciggie, Marguerite Churchhill, Mabel[?] Coleman[?], Carroll Nancy Danubear[?], Claudia Dell, and Shannon Dommocanon[?], 1930-1931, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Fox, Gibson[?], Yvonne Grey (negative and print), 1931 and undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Fawsett contest winner, Hackett, Georgia Hale, Lillian Hall, and Margorie Jones[?], 1931, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Avis[?] Johnson[?] and Lucile Ricksen[?] (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Gwen Kenyon[?], Kimberley-Eve, Mae Kaill, Natile Kingston, Evelyn Knopp, Maxine, Col[?] William[?] McBaur[?], Helen Mack, and Dorothy MacRaill[?], undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Nixon, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Anita Page, D.[?] Page, Irene Rich and Nick Stuart, 1931 and undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Clair Windsor, Windsor Group and Wright, 1931 and undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Oversize--Barkly, Joan, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Oversize--Earle, Madeline, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Oversize--Kenyon, Gwen, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Oversize--Kimberely, Eve, undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Oversize--Morris, Ann, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Oversize--Richards, Marta, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Oversize--Miss Wallace, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Oversize--Allen, Elizabeth, head and hat, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Oversize--Character study samples, 1. Baxter, 2. Pirate[?], 3. Roosevelt, 4.Pirate[?], with note "are these all Warren Baxter?", undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, red nightgown, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Oversize--Barclay, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, 1/2 view, hands to face, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, eyes turned, large hat, 1937 June 1 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Oversize--Barclay, pajamas, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Oversize--Barclay, hat, cigarette, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, large head, straight face, bare shoulders, drapes and flowers over one side, undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, bare back, smiling, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Oversize--Barclay, Joan, scarf over one shoulder, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Oversize--Miss Dale, undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Oversize--Damon, Margaret and Dr. Cunningham, undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Oversize--Earle, Madeline, head on chair, flowered desk, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Oversize--Garnor, Janet, undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Oversize--Garnor, Janet, with fan, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Oversize--Miss Wallace, white and gold drape over head, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Oversize--Lang, Temple, Willie Wonkle[?], undated (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Oversize--Gaynor, Janet, with flower lei, undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - B. Anonymous subjects, ca. 1920-1946
    This subseries consists of black and white negatives featuring anonymous models and persons photographed by Edwin Bower Hesser. These negatives include women, men, and children in casual, semi-formal, and formal attire; nude, semi-nude, and erotic modeling women; women in costume and festive attire; various animals; women in bathing suits; women in winter clothes; men in military uniforms; couples; models with various props; various exterior scenes; theatrical and film scenes; and women dancing. Files are arranged in alphabetically according to gender and attire.
    - Children (1 of 2), ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified young boys and girls.
    - Children (2 of 2), ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Couple A, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified couple. Includes shots of man wearing a turban and woman in a veil. Also includes solo shots.
    - Couple B, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified young couple. Both are wearing casual attire.
    - Couple C, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified middle-aged couple. Both are wearing casual attire. Both are not smiling and dressed in business attire. Includes solo shots.
    - Couple D, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified older couple. Man is wearing a suit, while woman wears formal gown and fur coat and hat. Includes solo shots.
    - Couple E, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified smiling older couple. Man is wearing a suit, while woman wears business attire. Includes solo shots.
    - Couple F, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified couple. Man is wearing a suit and glasses while woman wears fur trimmed dress.
    - Couple G, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified older couple. Man is wearing glasses and suit, while woman wears a business suit. Both are not smiling.
    - Couple H, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      4 x 5" black and white portraits and head shots of unidentified older couple. Man is wearing military uniform, while woman wears semi-formal attire. Includes test print.
    - Modeling couples--assorted, ca. 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 1)